A Guide to the Fairfax County Office of Public Affairs Photograph Collection, 1962-2009
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
- Series 6: Photo and Negative File, 1987-2006
  - Louis B. Wagner Lifetime Achievement Award, 1999 November 15 (Box 19)
  - 11-yr-old Pioneer Baseball Babe Ruth “Bambino” Team (Kauffman), 1999 November 22 (Box 19)
  - Matthew Harper (Dix), 1999 November 22 (Box 19)
  - Centreville High School Girls Tennis (Frey), 1999 November 22 (Box 19)
  - National Family Week (Hanley), 1999 November 22 (Box 19)
  - Lahey Family/Fred Crabtree (Dix), 1999 November 22 (Box 19)
  - AIDS Awareness Day (Hanley), 1999 November 22 (Box 19)
  - J.R Stockyards Inn 25th anniversary (Dix/Connolly), 1999 November 22 (Box 19)
  - F&R’s Urban Search & Rescue Team - Turkey (Hanley), 1999 December 6 (Box 19)
  - F&R’s Fight fighter Combat Challenge Team & Rodeo Team (Hanley), 1999 December 6 (Box 19)
  - James Madison High School 40th anniversary (Dix), 1999 December 6 (Box 19)
  - Katie Ruckert & Mary Kovarik (Dix), 1999 December 6 (Box 19)
  - 110-lb & 125-lb McLean Mustangs Youth Football Teams (Mendelsohn), 1999 December 6 (Box 19)
  - Gladelle Hardenbergh, Cheryl Reames & MaryLou Sybert (Dix), 1999 December 6 (Box 19)
  - Joyce Reilly Clautice (Hyland), 1999 December 6 (Box 19)
  - Tricia Hutcherson (Mendelsohn/Hanley), 1999 December 6 (Box 19)
  - Wes “Mickey” Kendrick (Hyland), 1999 December 6 (Box 19)
  - Gene Schaeffer (Hyland), 1999 December 6 (Box 19)
  - Claude Moore Colonial Farm (Mendelsohn), 1999 December 6 (Box 19)
  - Reston 2000 Task Force (Dix), 1999 December 6 (Box 19)
  - Dix’ staff (Dix), 1999 December 6 (Box 19)
  - Mark Looney - Chamber of Commerce (Hanley), 1999 December 6 (Box 19)
  - Marcus Simon (Hanley), 1999 December 6 (Box 19)
  - Inauguration Ceremony - Fairfax County Board of Supervisors & Constitutional Officers, 1999 December 20 (Box 20)
  - Eric Swain (Hanley), 2000 January 10 (Box 21)
  - Year of the Child 2000 (Hanley), 2000 January 10 (Box 21)
  - Francis Dall (Bulova), 2000 January 10 (Box 21)
  - Carl Peed (Mendelsohn), 2000 January 10 (Box 21)
  - Officer Scott Collins (Kauffman), 2000 January 10 (Box 21)
  - African American History Month (Hanley), 2000 January 24 (Box 21)
  - The Police Department - Best Traffic Safety Program (Hanley), 2000 January 24 (Box 21)
  - David C. Hobson (Hanley), 2000 January 24 (Box 21)
  - Don Emerson (Bulova), 2000 January 24 (Box 21)
  - Talent House Private School (Connolly), 2000 January 24 (Box 21)
  - Richard Bissell (Mendelsohn), 2000 January 24 (Box 21)
  - Ann W. Anderson - Retirement for Office of Public Affairs, 2000 January 24 (Box 21)
  - Officer John Burdette (Connolly), 2000 February 7 (Box 21)
  - Department of Information Technology (Hyland), 2000 February 7 (Box 21)
  - Lowe’s Home Improvement Warehouse, Inc., & Home Safety Council (Kauffman), 2000 February 28 (Box 21)
  - Women’s History Month (Hanley), 2000 February 28 (Box 21)
  - Mr. Alvin Thomas (Mendelsohn), 2000 February 28 (Box 21)
  - Deputy Charles E. Michael, Jr. (Connolly), 2000 February 28 (Box 21)
  - Lori Lewis and Susan Malone, Police Department (Bulova), 2000 February 28 (Box 21)
  - NET Teen Center (McConnell), 2000 March 13 (Box 21)
  - Developmental Disabilities Inclusion Month (Bulova), 2000 March 13 (Box 21)
  - Celebrate Diversity Month (Hanley), 2000 March 13 (Box 21)
  - Purchasing Month (Hanley), 2000 March 13 (Box 21)
  - Bernie Cieplak (McConnell), 2000 March 13 (Box 21)
  - Robbie Benton (McConnell), 2000 March 13 (Box 21)
  - TB Awareness Day (Hanley), 2000 March 13 (Box 21)
  - South Lakes High School Drama Department (Hudgins), 2000 March 27 (Box 21)
  - John Paul Macias (Connolly), 2000 March 27 (Box 21)
  - Census Day - April 1, 2000 (Hanley), 2000 March 27 (Box 21)
  - National Immunization Month - April 2000 (Hanley), 2000 March 27 (Box 21)
  - Millard H. Robbins, Jr. (Frey), 2000 March 27 (Box 21)
  - Patricia Woolsey (Hanley), 2000 March 27 (Box 21)
  - Ecostewards - Peter Kelsey & Jeanette Stewart (Connolly), 2000 March 27 (Box 21)
  - Carla Pittman (Kauffman), 2000 March 27 (Box 21)
  - Chantilly High School Girls’ Gymnastics Team (Frey), 2000 April 3 (Box 21)
  - Oakton Cougar Bands Day (Connolly), 2000 April 3 (Box 21)
  - Golden Girls Softball Teams (Connolly), 2000 April 3 (Box 21)
  - Building Safety Week (Frey), 2000 April 3 (Box 21)
  - Child Abuse Prevention Month (Hanley), 2000 April 3 (Box 21)
  - Northern Virginia Soul & Water Conservation District and DPWES (Kauffman), 2000 April 3 (Box 21)
  - Public Health Week (Hanley), 2000 April 3 (Box 21)
  - Spirit of ADA (Americans with Disabilities Act) Torch Relay (Frey), 2000 April 24 (Box 21)
  - Older Americans Month (Hanley), 2000 April 24 (Box 21)
  - Asian/Pacific American Heritage Month (Hanley), 2000 April 24 (Box 21)
  - Community Development Week (Hanley), 2000 April 24 (Box 21)
  - Million Mom March Day (Hanley), 2000 May 8 (Box 21)
  - Community Action Month (Hudgins), 2000 May 8 (Box 21)
  - Motorcycle Safety and Awareness Month (Hanley), 2000 May 8 (Box 21)
  - Mr. “Jess” Hendrix (Frey), 2000 May 8 (Box 21)
  - Foster Family Recognition Month (Hanley), 2000 May 8 (Box 21)
  - Stroke Awareness Month (Gross), 2000 May 8 (Box 21)
  - Leonard Wales (Connolly), 2000 May 8 (Box 21)
  - Garfield Elementary School (Kauffman), 2000 May 22 (Box 21)
  - Computer Sciences Corporation (Connolly), 2000 May 22 (Box 21)
  - Dr. Vera Blake, 2000 May 22 (Box 21)
  - Department of Family Services - “Nurturing Parenting Program” (Hyland), 2000 May 22 (Box 21)
  - Mildred Corbin (Kauffman), 2000 May 22 (Box 21)
  - Alma Walker Bushrod (Kauffman), 2000 May 22 (Box 21)
  - Early Intervention Month (Gross), 2000 May 22 (Box 21)
  - Centreville Volunteer Fire Department - 50th Anniversary (Frey), 2000 May 22 (Box 21)
  - National Public Work Week (Hanley), 2000 May 22 (Box 21)
  - Springfield Days (Kauffman), 2000 May 22 (Box 21)
  - United States Army Week (Hanley), 2000 June 5 (Box 21)
  - 2000 Lords and Ladies Fairfax (Hanley), 2000 June 5 (Box 21)
  - Sponsors, Host and Planning Cttee for Earth Day/Arbor Day (Bulova), 2000 June 5 (Box 21)
  - Mantua Elementary School and Burke School (Connolly), 2000 June 5 (Box 21)
  - Longfellow Middle School (Music, Math & Chess) (Mendelsohn), 2000 June 5 (Box 21)
  - Hayfield Hawks Boys’ Varsity Basketball Team (Kauffman), 2000 June 5 (Box 21)
  - Gail Ritchie (Bulova), 2000 June 5 (Box 21)
  - Pine Ridge Park Watch (Gross), 2000 June 5 (Box 21)
  - McLean High School Highlanders Senior Men’s Four Rowing Team (Mendelsohn), 2000 June 26 (Box 21)
  - Amanda Koppel (Frey), 2000 June 26 (Box 21)
  - Kevin Greenlief (Hanley), 2000 June 26 (Box 21)
  - Girl Power Day (Kauffman), 2000 June 26 (Box 21)
  - Maurice A. Sovern (Hudgins), 2000 June 26 (Box 21)
  - Judy Azzara (Hudgins), 2000 June 26 (Box 21)
  - Office of Partnerships - Eight Exceptional Women Graduates (Hanley), 2000 June 26 (Box 21)
  - Steven Young (Hudgins), 2000 June 26 (Box 21)
  - Forest Edge Elementary/Odyssey of the Mind teams (Hudgins), 2000 July 10 (Box 21)
  - John E. Casagrade (Bulova), 2000 July 10 (Box 21)
  - Weber Associates (Hanley), 2000 July 10 (Box 21)
  - Linda Clark (Hanley), 2000 July 10 (Box 21)
  - Helen Fitzgerald (Gross), 2000 July 10 (Box 21)
  - Columbia Lighthouse for the Blind/Fairfax County Public Library (Hanley), 2000 July 24 (Box 21)
  - Spirit of the Americans with Disabilities Act Torch Relay (Connolly), 2000 July 24 (Box 21)
  - Frank Dutton (Mendelsohn), 2000 July 24 (Box 21)
  - 95th Anniversary of the National Capital Chapter of the American Red Cross (Connolly), 2000 July 24 (Box 21)
  - Dr. Loretta Webb (Hudgins, Conolly and Mendelsohn), 2000 July 24 (Box 21)
  - Dr. Joan Volpe, 2000 July 24 (Box 21)
  - Sneak Peek Committee (Connolly), 2000 July 24 (Box 21)
  - Mayor Jane Seeman (Hudgins), 2000 August 7 (Box 21)
  - Gordon Brown (Bulova) NACo Awards (Hyland), 2000 August 7 (Box 21)
  - Ruth Johnson (Frey and Bulova), 2000 August 7 (Box 21)
  - Michael Long (Connolly), 2000 August 7 (Box 21)
  - Aubrey Tarkington (Connolly, Hyland and McConnell), 2000 August 7 (Box 21)
  - Victoria (Vicky) Wingert (Hudgins), 2000 August 7 (Box 21)
  - Rickey Harris (Frey), 2000 August 7 (Box 21)
  - Joshua Thomas (Frey), 2000 September 11 (Box 21)
  - Harold Wilson (Hyland), 2000 September 11 (Box 21)
  - Reston Multicultural Festival Day (Hudgins), 2000 September 11 (Box 21)
  - Hispanic Heritage Month (Hanley), 2000 September 11 (Box 21)
  - Brian Smith (Gross), 2000 September 25 (Box 21)
  - McLean Little League major All-Star Softball Team (Mendelsohn), 2000 September 25 (Box 21)
  - Sheriff’s Office Plane Pull Team (Hanley), 2000 September 25 (Box 21)
  - Law Enforcement Mtn. Bike Comp./Child Bicycle Safety Awareness Day (McConnell), 2000 September 25 (Box 21)
  - NOVA Turn Off the Violence Week (Hanley), 2000 September 25 (Box 21)
  - McLean Community Center 25th Anniversary (Mendelsohn), 2000 September 25 (Box 21)
  - Oakton Boys AAA Basketball Team (Connolly), 2000 September 25 (Box 21)
  - Crime Prevention Unit-Police Department (Connolly), 2000 September 25 (Box 21)
  - Pine Spring Elementary School (Connolly), 2000 September 25 (Box 21)
  - John Freeman and the Kingsley Community Coalition (Connolly), 2000 September 25 (Box 21)
  - Robert Andrews (Mendelsohn), 2000 October 16 (Box 21)
  - Cecilia Lammers (Mendelsohn), 2000 October 16 (Box 21)
  - Carla Convery (Hyland), 2000 October 16 (Box 21)
  - VolunteerFest® Day (Hanley), 2000 October 16 (Box 21)
  - Mary Simpson (McConnell), 2000 October 16 (Box 21)
  - Gunston Heights and Wiley communities (Hyland), 2000 October 16 (Box 21)
  - Disability Employment Awareness Month (Hanley), 2000 October 16 (Box 21)
  - Natural Resources Week (Hanley), 2000 October 16 (Box 21)
  - Character Counts! Week (Gross), 2000 October 16 (Box 21)
  - Mattie Brown Day (McConnell/Frey), 2000 October 30 (Box 21)
  - Healthy Families of Fairfax (McConnell), 2000 October 30 (Box 21)
  - American Indian Heritage Month (Hanley), 2000 October 30 (Box 21)
  - Wesley Housing Development Corporation (Hanley), 2000 October 30 (Box 21)
  - Celiac Awareness Month (Hanley), 2000 October 30 (Box 21)
  - Computer Learning Month (Hanley), 2000 October 30 (Box 21)
  - Library Foundation IMLS Grant and partners Hanley, 2000 October 30 (Box 21)
  - America Recycles Day (Hanley), 2000 October 30 (Box 21)
  - Dorothy Cousineau, Andy Szakos and Dept. of Transportation (Hudgins), 2000 October 30 (Box 21)
  - Substance Abuse Awareness Week (Hanley), 2000 October 30 (Box 21)
  - Judge F. Bruce Back (Hyland), 2000 November 20 (Box 21)
  - Washington Area Conference on Telework (Connolly), 2000 November 20 (Box 21)
  - Hollin Hill community (Hyland), 2000 November 20 (Box 21)
  - Capt. James Charron, MPO Edward O’Carroll and West Springfield Police station (McConnell), 2000 November 20 (Box 21)
  - Detective Richard Perez (McConnell), 2000 November 20 (Box 21)
  - Claudia Thompson-Deahl, 2000 November 20 (Box 21)
  - Vivian Watts (Bulova), 2000 December 4 (Box 21)
  - VA Affordable Housing Mgmt. Assoc. Posters Contest (Kauffman), 2000 December 4 (Box 21)
  - 50th Anniversary of Park Authority (Hanley), 2000 December 4 (Box 21)
  - Dying in America planning group and SOLACE (Bulova), 2000 December 4 (Box 21)
  - Nick Palatiello (Mendelsohn), 2000 December 4 (Box 21)
  - Falls Church High School Culinary Arts (Connolly), 2000 December 4 (Box 21)
  - Election Page program (Hanley), 2000 December 4 (Box 21)
  - AIDS Awareness Week (Hanley), 2000 December 4 (Box 21)
  - Centreville High School Girls’ Tennis Team (Frey), 2000 December 4 (Box 21)
  - Centreville Community Foundation (Frey), 2000 December 4 (Box 21)
  - Mid-Atlantic Motorcycle Safety Rodeo (McConnell), 2000 December 4 (Box 21)
  - Fx.Co.-Southwest VA Exchange Program (Hudgins), 2000 December 11 (Box 21)
  - 4H Club Hoofers and heifers (Frey), 2000 December 11 (Box 21)
  - Friends of George Mason Library (Gross), 2000 December 11 (Box 21)
  - Armand Malo (Hanley), 2000 December 11 (Box 21)
  - Bill Cramer (Hudgins), 2000 December 11 (Box 21)
  - Jay Jorgensen (Hyland), 2001 January 8 (Box 22)
  - Diane Barrett (McConnell), 2001 January 8 (Box 22)
  - Allyn Anderson-Sodowsky (Frey), 2001 January 8 (Box 22)
  - Centreville High School Girls’ Lacrosse (Frey), 2001 January 8 (Box 22)
  - Lady Bruins Cross Country Team (Bulova), 2001 January 22 (Box 22)
  - African American History Month (Hanley), 2001 January 22 (Box 22)
  - Judith Downer (Mendelsohn), 2001 January 22 (Box 22)
  - Donate-A-Phone (Connolly), 2001 January 22 (Box 22)
  - Fairfax County Police (IACP Award) & MPO James D. Bean, 2001 January 22 (Box 22)
  - Paisley Callow (Hudgins), 2001 February 5 (Box 22)
  - Carla Pittman (Gross), 2001 February 5 (Box 22)
  - Centreville High School Football Team (Frey), 2001 February 5 (Box 22)
  - Geographic Information System Program (GIS) (Hyland), 2001 February 5 (Box 22)
  - Chairman Hanley (Washingtonian of the Year) (Hudgins/Connolly), 2001 February 5 (Box 22)
  - Women’s History Month (Hanley), 2001 February 26 (Box 22)
  - Bob Lowey (Hyland/Kauffman), 2001 February 26 (Box 22)
  - Debra Andrews (Hyland), 2001 February 26 (Box 22)
  - Fairfax Bar Association (Mendelsohn/Hyland), 2001 March 5 (Box 22)
  - Christian Relief Services (Hyland), 2001 March 5 (Box 22)
  - Adopt-A-Family Partnership (Hanley), 2001 March 5 (Box 22)
  - Including People with Developmental Disabilities (Hanley), 2001 March 5 (Box 22)
  - Purchasing Month (Hanley), 2001 March 5 (Box 22)
  - Elena Kopersak (Bulova), 2001 March 19 (Box 22)
  - Jennifer Seiler (Kauffman), 2001 March 19 (Box 22)
  - Alan Webb (Hudgins), 2001 March 19 (Box 22)
  - Celebrate Diversity Month (Hanley), 2001 March 19 (Box 22)
  - Immunization Month (Hanley), 2001 March 19 (Box 22)
  - TB Awareness Day (Hanley), 2001 March 19 (Box 22)
  - Madeira School Girls’ Swim and Dive Team (Mendelsohn), 2001 April 2 (Box 22)
  - MK Jennings and Kay Lauren Miller (Hanley), 2001 April 2 (Box 22)
  - Fairfax County Volunteer Recognition Day (Hanley), 2001 April 2 (Box 22)
  - Child Abuse Prevention Month (Hanley), 2001 April 2 (Box 22)
  - Fair Housing Month (Hanley), 2001 April 2 (Box 22)
  - Public Health Week (Hanley), 2001 April 2 (Box 22)
  - Organ and Tissue Donor Awareness Week (Gross), 2001 April 2 (Box 22)
  - Building Safety Week (Frey), 2001 April 2 (Box 22)
  - George Mason University Men’s Basketball Team (Frey), 2001 April 30 (Box 22)
  - Jim Hart (Frey), 2001 April 30 (Box 22)
  - Elizabeth Hartwell (Hyland), 2001 April 30 (Box 22)
  - Co-Housing Month (Hudgins), 2001 April 30 (Box 22)
  - Langley High School Girl’ Swim and Dive Team (Mendelsohn), 2001 April 30 (Box 22)
  - Older Americans Month (Frey), 2001 April 30 (Box 22)
  - Soil and Water Stewardship Week (Hanley), 2001 April 30 (Box 22)
  - Office of the Sheriff (Connolly), 2001 April 30 (Box 22)
  - Asian/Pacific American Heritage Month (Hanley), 2001 April 30 (Box 22)
  - Provider Appreciation Day (Hanley), 2001 May 7 (Box 22)
  - Girls’ Rights Week (Frey), 2001 May 7 (Box 22)
  - Community Action Month (Connolly), 2001 May 7 (Box 22)
  - Foster Care and Foster Family Recognition Month, 2001 May 7 (Box 22)
  - Safe Kids Week (Hanley), 2001 May 7 (Box 22)
  - Bike to Work Week (Hanley), 2001 May 7 (Box 22)
  - Lords and Ladies Fairfax (Hanley), 2001 May 21 (Box 22)
  - Springfield Days (Kauffman), 2001 May 21 (Box 22)
  - Public Works Week (Hanley), 2001 May 21 (Box 22)
  - Carl Bly (Frey), 2001 June 11 (Box 22)
  - Frank Mehm (Mendelsohn), 2001 June 11 (Box 22)
  - Doris Leadbetter (Mendelsohn), 2001 June 11 (Box 22)
  - Prentice Christian (Hudgins), 2001 June 11 (Box 22)
  - Katie McLean (Hyland), 2001 June 11 (Box 22)
  - Shelter House (Gross), 2001 June 11 (Box 22)
  - Hepatitis Awareness Day (Hanley), 2001 June 11 (Box 22)
  - Bruce Bach (Mendelsohn), 2001 June 25 (Box 22)
  - Andrea Warner (Connolly), 2001 June 25 (Box 22)
  - Girl Power Day (Hudgins), 2001 June 25 (Box 22)
  - MathCounts Competition (Mendelsohn), 2001 June 25 (Box 22)
  - Keira Carlstrom and the Oakton HS Girls’/Boys’ Cross-Country Teams (Hudgins), 2001 June 25 (Box 22)
  - McLean High School Concert Band (Mendelsohn), 2001 June 25 (Box 22)
  - Providence District Senior and Law Enforcement Together (S.A.L.T)(Connolly), 2001 June 25 (Box 22)
  - Tom Bartelt, 2001 June 25 (Box 22)
  - 2001 Citizens Advisory Committee on Reapportionment (Connolly), 2001 July 9 (Box 22)
  - Carol Franz (Gross), 2001 July 9 (Box 22)
  - Centreville High School Girls’ Lacrosse Team (Frey), 2001 July 9 (Box 22)
  - Starr Karl (Frey), 2001 July 9 (Box 22)
  - Men’s Firefighter Combat Challenge Team (Connolly), 2001 July 23 (Box 22)
  - Fairfax Leadership and Resiliency Program (Frey), 2001 July 23 (Box 22)
  - Bonnie Hudson (Bulova), 2001 July 23 (Box 22)
  - Carl Bianchi (Bulova), 2001 July 23 (Box 22)
  - Nottoway Nights 2001 (Connolly), 2001 July 23 (Box 22)
  - Top Cop Fitness Challenge (Hanley), 2001 July 23 (Box 22)
  - Milagros - The Miracle Dog (Hanley/Frey), 2001 August 6 (Box 22)
  - Medical Care for Children Partnership (Hanley), 2001 August 6 (Box 22)
  - Fairfax Stars 12-Year-Old Girls’ Basketball Team (Frey), 2001 August 6 (Box 22)
  - Vincent Keane (Hyland), 2001 August 6 (Box 22)
  - Earth Day/Arbor Day Sponsors (Bulova), 2001 August 6 (Box 22)
  - National Night Out (Gross/McConnell), 2001 August 6 (Box 22)
  - National Marrow Awareness Month (Hanley), 2001 August 6 (Box 22)
  - Allen Hogge (Hyland), 2001 August 6 (Box 22)
  - Odyssey of Mind Teams, 2001 September 10 (Box 22)
  - MPO Josh Brown, 2001 September 10 (Box 22)
  - Fairfax Choral Society Anniversary/Choral Awareness Week, 2001 September 10 (Box 22)
  - Certificate of Achievement for Excellence in Financial Reporting, 2001 September 10 (Box 22)
  - Hispanic Heritage Month, 2001 September 10 (Box 22)
  - Ovarian Cancer Awareness Month, 2001 September 10 (Box 22)
  - Child Auto Safety Program Coalition, 2001 September 10 (Box 22)
  - 9/11 Day of Remembrance Ceremony, 2001 September 14 (Box 22)
  - Fairfax County Park Authority, 2001 September 24 (Box 22)
  - Northern Virginia Conservation Trust, 2001 September 24 (Box 22)
  - Basim Naga, 2001 September 24 (Box 22)
  - MPO James F. Kelly, Jr., 2001 September 24 (Box 22)
  - Disability Employment Awareness Month, 2001 September 24 (Box 22)
  - McLean Little League Major All-Star Girls’ Softball Team, 2001 October 1 (Box 22)
  - Fairfax Stars 11 -year-old and 13 -year-old Girls’ Basketball Teams, 2001 October 1 (Box 22)
  - Robinson High School Distributive Education Clubs of America/Marketing Group, 2001 October 1 (Box 22)
  - Operation Tools for Success Partnership, 2001 October 1 (Box 22)
  - Mental Illness Awareness Week, 2001 October 1 (Box 22)
  - Turn Off the Violence Week, 2001 October 1 (Box 22)
  - Fire Prevention Week, 2001 October 1 (Box 22)
  - Office for Children 25th Anniversary, 2001 October 1 (Box 22)
  - Delegate Jim Scott and the HJR 276 Committee (Connolly), 2001 October 22 (Box 22)
  - Puneet Gambhir (Mendelsohn), 2001 October 22 (Box 22)
  - Chantilly Cannons (Hanley), 2001 October 22 (Box 22)
  - VolunteerFest® Day (Hanley), 2001 October 22 (Box 22)
  - Substance Abuse Awareness Week (Hanley), 2001 October 22 (Box 22)
  - Inova Fairfax Hospital (Transplant Center anniversary) (Hanley), 2001 October 22 (Box 22)
  - Sharon Kelso (Hanley), 2001 October 22 (Box 22)
  - America Recycles Day (Hanley), 2001 October 22 (Box 22)
  - Crestwood Elementary School (Kauffman), 2001 November 19 (Box 22)
  - Welch Sisters Wash America (Gross), 2001 November 19 (Box 22)
  - Bonnie White Rupp (Hudgins), 2001 November 19 (Box 22)
  - Holmes Run Acres Community (Connolly), 2001 November 19 (Box 22)
  - Jack Evans (Hyland), 2001 November 19 (Box 22)
  - Reston Multicultural Festival (Hudgins), 2001 November 19 (Box 22)
  - Network Against Family Abuse (NAFA)(Gross), 2001 November 19 (Box 22)
  - American Indian Heritage Month (Hanley), 2001 November 19 (Box 22)
  - Vienna American, 2001 December 3 (Box 22)
  - Little League All-Stars (Hudgins), 2001 December 3 (Box 22)
  - Langley High School Golf Team (Mendelsohn), 2001 December 3 (Box 22)
  - Public Safety Personnel (9/11 Response) (Hanley), 2001 December 3 (Box 22)
  - Election Pages (Hanley), 2001 December 3 (Box 22)
  - Steve Brown (Frey), 2001 December 3 (Box 22)
  - George Mason Week (Hanley), 2001 December 3 (Box 22)
  - AIDS Awareness Week (Hanley), 2001 December 3 (Box 22)
  - Greater Reston Chamber of Commerce (Hudgins), 2001 December 3 (Box 22)
  - Robert Moore (Frey), 2001 December 3 (Box 22)
  - National Mentoring Month (Mendelsohn), 2002 January 7 (Box 23)
  - Isaac Ho’opi’i (Mendelsohn), 2002 January 7 (Box 23)
  - Kris Knodt and Gilbert Nelson (Bulova), 2002 January 7 (Box 23)
  - Kathy Benli and Jacqueline Smith (Kauffman), 2002 January 7 (Box 23)
  - John Palatiello (Mendelsohn), 2002 January 7 (Box 23)
  - Barbara Naef (Hudgins), 2002 January 7 (Box 23)
  - Candy Brown, Rita Kaufman and Sarah West (Hanley), 2002 January 7 (Box 23)
  - Woodley Hills Elementary School (Hyland), 2002 January 28 (Box 23)
  - Mack Rhoades (Hyland), 2002 January 28 (Box 23)
  - Roberts Parkway Overpass Task Force (Bulova), 2002 January 28 (Box 23)
  - African-American History Month (Hanley), 2002 January 28 (Box 23)
  - Reston Youth Football Association Anklebiter Team (Hudgins), 2002 February 11 (Box 23)
  - Warren Carmichael (Kauffman), 2002 February 11 (Box 23)
  - Mark Martino and Roy Holder (Bulova), 2002 February 11 (Box 23)
  - National Children’s Dental Health Month (Hanley), 2002 February 11 (Box 23)
  - National Engineer Week (Hanley), 2002 February 11 (Box 23)
  - Recognition of County’s Senior Mgmt. Team for #1 rating Governing (Hanley), 2002 February 11 (Box 23)
  - Dulles Corridor Land Use Task Force (Hudgins), 2002 February 25 (Box 23)
  - Kim Rabinowitch and Lenard Wolfenstein (Connolly), 2002 February 25 (Box 23)
  - Red Cross Month (Hanley), 2002 February 25 (Box 23)
  - Women’s History Month (Hanley), 2002 February 25 (Box 23)
  - People with Developmental Disabilities Month (Bulova), 2002 March 4 (Box 23)
  - National Girl Scout Week (Gross), 2002 March 4 (Box 23)
  - Colon Cancer Awareness Month (Hanley), 2002 March 4 (Box 23)
  - Purchasing Month (Hanley), 2002 March 4 (Box 23)
  - David Molchany (Hyland), 2002 March 18 (Box 23)
  - NOVA Hawks Football Team (Kauffman), 2002 March 18 (Box 23)
  - Celebratge4 Diversity Month (Hanley), 2002 March 18 (Box 23)
  - Mary Anne Gatton (Hudgins), 2002 March 18 (Box 23)
  - John Callaghan (Hudgins), 2002 March 18 (Box 23)
  - Crossroads Program (Kauffman), 2002 March 18 (Box 23)
  - TB Awareness Day (Hanley), 2002 March 18 (Box 23)
  - Public Health Week (Hanley), 2002 March 18 (Box 23)
  - Madeira School Girls’ Swim and Dive Team (Mendelsohn), 2002 April 8 (Box 23)
  - Electrical, Mechanical and Plumbing Advisory Boards (Frey), 2002 April 8 (Box 23)
  - Thomas Davis Rust (Mendelsohn), 2002 April 8 (Box 23)
  - Immunization Month (Hanley), 2002 April 8 (Box 23)
  - Women and Girls’ Wellness Month (Gross), 2002 April 8 (Box 23)
  - McLean Orchestra (Mendelsohn), 2002 April 8 (Box 23)
  - Volunteer Recognition Day (Hanley), 2002 April 8 (Box 23)
  - National Crime Victims’ Right Week (Hanley), 2002 April 8 (Box 23)
  - Organ and Tissue Donation Awareness Week (Gross), 2002 April 8 (Box 23)
  - Oak Hill Elementary School (Frey), 2002 April 8 (Box 23)
  - Fair Housing Month (Hanley), 2002 April 8 (Box 23)
  - Child Abuse Prevention Month (Hanley), 2002 April 8 (Box 23)
  - International Building Safety Week (Frey), 2002 April 8 (Box 23)
  - Firefighter Combat Challenge Team (Connolly), 2002 April 29 (Box 23)
  - Bike to Work Day (Hudgins/Gross), 2002 April 29 (Box 23)
  - Michelle Peyser (Frey), 2002 April 29 (Box 23)